uncle get up
well wake up already
wake up leave me alone
Kansana I needed a little from life
I just wanted to be free
well
that's all
but the load that I wanted to throw off
it rests on my shoulders
when did they have time
unexpectedly
Donsik come over
why come here
bend over why
what's there
when did you meet your wife in college
and before her you had girls
of course
and how much
you and I are so different
this is news
why are you wearing glasses
want to see the world through the eyes of a criminal
and by the way, they don’t suit you, I know
help you
you are from panju school yes
follow me
what the hell are you moving
what do you allow yourself
Do you at least have a warrant?
what do you want you are not arrested
we just came to visit a friend and find out something
what other friend
what to find out
you'll see now
wait here
damn you can go
stop
you don't know Son had boyfriends guys
Woo Kang Seong
I don't know about guys
but she definitely hated someone
maybe you
come on no nonsense
Hinhap's birthday is coming soon
Let's celebrate November 1st
I don't want
why
I've never mentioned it before
sorry then you have no choice
meet me before the party
just you and me
I like the glitter
I just bought a terrible color
why is it better to erase
Well, no, but if my wife came
Gina no training for them today
why are you at school
Why are you just so depressed, what’s wrong with you?
nothing
why is it so strange with her?
jiuk
we have a case of rape of a minor Sumin
she can handle it, she could use some help
who is the victim
a week ago
I came to visit one of my friends
we were both trainees and trained together
we drank a little
and then I passed out for a while
my underwear
was worn inside out
where was that guy
he wrote that he needed to go somewhere
Have you had sexual intercourse before?
no
Well, why is she lying?
what are you talking about?
yes so
we'll visit that guy tomorrow
We're probably already late
what kind of children are they?
even I didn't behave like that
what are you muttering there?
I'm sick of this school
I graduated 1,000,000 years ago
I understand there's been so much going on at school lately
detective han hello
hello hello
she's a virgin
ohh
how is Sana
still in the hospital
The guys and I wanted to visit her, would you mind?
it's too early
I understand
I'm watching
you are now wearing glasses
it suits you very well
well of course
your ears are red
do you know a student with a hanyou
hanyou yes
Suhan Yoo what is your relationship with Yoon Jina we
just acquaintances
we interned together before
on the evening of September 20th
you were drinking together at your house
where are your parents
abroad I came to Korea to become a singer
that's why I live alone
Minors are not allowed to drink
impudent or what?
sorry detective
I'm on edge because of school
you are being questioned in a sexual assault case
you understand
Gina said so
we had nothing
she's not my type
children now are something with something
and they look so cute
you just have to dig and you'll find something
okay stop staring
I was going to tell
give it back
this is physical evidence
I can't give them to you
and you can carry Yuleikas with you
I have to check
how do they work
Isn't that what criminologists are supposed to do?
yes
that's right
but when I put on these glasses
I realized that you didn't lie to me
it made me shiver
isn't it great
I believe you
and you don't believe me
get rid of glasses
calm down calm down
detective what about Sona
and my neighbor
you found glasses at the murder scene
still didn't understand
all these crimes are associated with glasses; wearing them is dangerous
well it sounds convincing
then it's even more worth checking
why are they dangerous
it's not the glasses themselves
but how they can affect you is what's the matter
everything is fine
안녕하세요
Hyun hap is a special girl
would you like to have dinner with me
what
I'll call you
hello, you arrived early, please sit down
yunjina
I personally brought this girl
but she didn't try very hard
so I told her to drop it
I don't force people to do that
what they don't like
can you tell me
what was the wife like
from my side
it's nice for me to say that
but she had no talent
to achieve something
she should have tried harder
but she didn't want to
but she really loved to relax
constantly invited other interns for drinks
met guys
it became clear that it would be of no use
the possibility of false accusations cannot be ruled out
don't rush to conclusions
I can't stand things like this
what are they like to figure out who is lying
besides they are both minors
this is a delicate matter
interrogations are limited
I wish we had something like
lie detector
yeah
this won't work
what are you talking about
yes so
by the way what are you
fell for teacher Sona what
Why did you suddenly decide that?
ok okay
she pissed me off
called and wanted to meet
I'll be debuting soon
I'm no longer an intern
can you look at the phone number?
yes
you deleted the message
washed clothes and underwear
which had traces of blood on it
but she announced it only a week later
you didn't think
that it could turn against you
I told you so
I didn't want to believe it
what happened
you can be punished for false denunciation
detective
I washed Jin's clothes
it's not her fault
sorry
Yoon Jina
I'm asking for the last time
you by force
not like that
Are you sure something happened between you and Sohanya?
don't hand over the case to the prosecutor
hey glasses
that's what you called me
I don't remember something like that
take it
not a gift but still
I looked at your file
it's not your fault
what happened
suddenly you thought so
this is what she looked like
in my memories she is different
want to find her
Sona said
may mother be alive
she would have found me
you say glasses
may be dangerous
but I'm sure they can be useful
you saved your neighbor
who are you trying to save?
Do you remember Yoon Jin from your class?
yes
she reported rape
case closed
thanks to glasses
Gina and Hyun Yu were not related
she claimed
that she was a virgin
but she has 4 lines
that's all
showed off
that you will become an idol
Yoon Jin finished the game
tells the truth
a week ago she had no lines
hello already handed over yoonjin's case
no, still working
wait for me why
let's start all over again
somehow I don't like all this
sohan yu
it's the police are you home
with Han Yu
hello detective
don't mind if we come in
yes come on in
you have
it's so clean here
means
this is where you drank that night
we were sitting on the sofa
she passed out
and I moved it
clear
alcohol bottles left
no, I don't keep trash at home
detectives
I have to get up early tomorrow morning
need to get some sleep
just in case
I came back and found glasses in the bathroom
what if someone set it up
so that the glasses get to you
It’s possible that no one knew that I was coming
not everything can be explained logically
the lines that I see
these glasses
I'm sure someone planted them at the crime scene
who needs it
how did you get here I just
I was passing by and noticed you
I followed you out of curiosity
but you suddenly disappeared from sight
you ignore me
why did you come back here
I forgot something here
you're not scared
it's creepy here
remember
I said that I see strange things
you have
above your head
don't scare
if only
I got a line with
I won't be so scared
what
if you're next to me
great start to the working day
but that's nothing
found
well understood thanks
how long will the examination take?
a day no less
how did you think of it
what to look for a sheet
on his bed
there was a sheet from another set
this alarmed me
and once he threw it away
good sheet
not in the trash but in a clothes container
he has something to hide
but I
I can't understand what
we adopt habits and behavior
through communication with other people
I'm sorry
on the way out
left class
please share, I'm hungry
I'll ask again
why did you throw away the sheet
I don't sleep on underwear
which someone used
how many times can you repeat
where is Gene's blood on the sheet?
I don’t know, maybe it’s coming out of my nose
or menstruation
Han Yu
I know
that you didn't do anything
I believe you why
girls can't resist handsome guys like us
yunjina was attracted to you
although you didn't care
I already said
she's not my type
a lot of people like her
but she didn’t want to come to me
I allowed I had some whiskey
I poured it and she drank it all
you had whiskey
what brand
I love whiskey
Glen fiddich what then
she got drunk
and said that she would not go home
I wanted another drink
I went to the store for beer
then she passed out
shouldn't have interfered
how did they sell you beer?
they didn't ask for documents
you can check
means glinfidih
CCTV cameras are only available in the parking lot
there are many apartments in the house
people go here and there
the time when the wife came
when hanyou went to the store and left in the morning
everything matches
how long did his trip to the store take 5 10 minutes
if at this time someone broke into the house
this would explain the appearance of the lines
it means she passed out before
how I drank beer
what lines
forget it
hey stop it
when they entered the house
about an hour ago
look here
there were no cameras in the backyard
no only here
rewind
1 2
3 4 5
was 6 is now 7
5 instead of four
1 2
these are the freaks
we're going outside
I'm so tired
took the cigarettes
no seriously you're kidding me
what the hell am I wasting my time on?
I need a lawyer
what are you typing with your hands?
please let me go home
I didn't do anything
please let me go
mom will kill me
please
ok I'll give you a ride let's go
detective my house is on the other side
I know
then where are we going
good car
do you like it
tell me where are you taking me
God what a long traffic light
why are we here
familiar place
detective about behind me
dansik
where will we have dinner?
let's drink soju jiuk
we don't have much time
Sohanya will have to let go
and there is no reason not to delay this
keep talking
but make your face more serious why
it's obvious
he's about to crack
you need to stay calm and wait a little
he won't last even 10 minutes
hey bomjo get out
that I won't go out
for a minute where are you taking me
not far we are already at the entrance
let's where are we going
please let me go home
just take a look at the crime scene and come back infected
consider yourself confessed
well you're an idiot
caught up with you quickly
yes
detective
I want to go home
I'll take you
but first to the station
why and where are the others?
everyone was released
why
we have nothing on them
what about me why won’t they let me go
and you
I set myself up
no no no
it's not fair
you can't do that
damn
calm down
bastards
detective
if I tell the truth
I won't be punished
well
everything depends on your words
I did it
but not alone
I'm not to blame for anything
hanyou organized it all
Gina has always been attractive
that day the guys asked me
how much will I pay
to sleep with her
I honestly thought
that we'll just have a drink together
but Han Yu slipped her something
detective that's all
Han Yu is the one who planned everything there
it wasn't just me
we all participated please
make an exception
Han Yu set it all up
I did it for the company
and this pervert
hanyou just sat and watched
it's yours
what did I find in your room, they climbed behind the fire extinguisher
you drugged Gin with this
how can you prove it
I kept it for fun
Let's see if the judge finds it funny
the rest confessed
four against 1
I didn't rape anyone
they did it
of course
but you arranged everything, you pervert
detective
they will be punished
I did everything in my power
the judge will decide the rest
I wish I could put glasses on the judge
so that he can see everything for himself
even with glasses
you can't see the whole truth
possible
if only I had as many lines as you
and I would become indifferent
this is an insult
you'll get home by yourself
I have an urgent matter
yes
what do you mean missing?
every time 1 and also you searched well
but we last time I found him on the roof
I think you should take a look
we haven't seen her before
and we don’t know how she got here
teacher Sona
dansik collect information on the Jin league
kushok kushok kushok
father
how
how did you end up here
Sona
it can't be
scumbag
don't you dare
take your hands off
Sana what did you do to her
bastard say something
bastard
how come
Sana
how could you
how will she live with this
I have a favor to ask
you can refuse
you like me
if I wanted to be with someone
then I could only choose you
here
I think you dropped it
detective
help me
I found information about your teacher Ligu
Gin doesn't exist
you understand
what do these lines mean
very soon
the whole world will turn red
I think we just gotta say
between the lines
what is real what is not
how are you so sure
still insecure by myself